Today in the United States,
the Supreme Court demolished Section 2
of the Voting Rights Act.
For those who don't know,
the Voting Rights Act passed in 1965
and it was a huge shift
in the direction of this country
in the wake,
or actually in the midst
of the civil rights movement.
Tonight for our weekly
Critical Thinking kickback
at 7 p.m. Eastern on my Patreon,
we'll be having a conversation
around voting, its efficacy.
What is the reason why
they're gutting these rights?
Why is Section 2 important?
We're going to talk about
voting on various levels
and we're going to talk about,
most importantly,
what does voting mean to you
and what does you voting
mean to the establishment?
So join us 7 p.m. Eastern
over at the Seals Squad.
That's patreon.com backslash Amanda Seals.
Yes, this is Vintage H&M.
Let's get it.
Support a real one.